A different set of jaws.
The Rocky Horror Picture Show is a comedy, science
fiction, fantasy film directed by Jim Sharman.
After getting a flat tire in the middle of nowhere, newly engaged couple Brad and
Janet encounter the eerie mansion of the flamboyant, seductive Dr.
Frank-N-Furter and a variety of eccentric characters.
Through elaborate dance and rock music, the mad scientist
unveils his latest creation: a perfect, muscular man.
Dr. Frank-N-Furter, played by Tim Curry.
Janet Weiss, played by Susan Sarandon.
Brad Majors, played by Barry Bostwick.
Riff Raff, played by Richard O'Brien.
Magenta, played by Patricia Quinn.
Columbia, played by Nell Campbell.
The Rocky Horror Picture Show is the original soundtrack album to the 1975 film The Rocky
Horror Picture Show, an adaptation of the 1973 musical The Rocky Horror Show.
The 1975 soundtrack album was released by Ode
Records and produced by Richard Hartley.
It should not be confused with The Rocky Horror Show album, a recording of the
theatrical music by Tim Curry and the original cast from The Roxy Theatre.
The latter album was released in 1974, also by Ode Records.
The film explores themes of sexual identity, rock 'n'
roll, transvestism, time warp, transylvania.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and thought_provoking.